Upton Sinclair Miscellaneous Materials VII: Articles about Sinclair and His Works, 1906-1965 PS3537.I85 (InU-Li-VAE1864)
Lilly Library
Upton Sinclair Miscellaneous Materials VII: Articles about Sinclair and His Works
1906-1965
1957
Lilly Library
PS3537.I85 (InU-Li-VAE1864)
324 Items
This collection consists of articles about Upton Sinclair and his works, from various periodicals.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Biographical Note
Upton Sinclair, 1878-1968, author, is best-known for his classic muck-raking novel The Jungle, which exposed labor and sanitary conditions in the U.S. meatpacking industry.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by call number.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of articles about Upton Sinclair and his works, from various periodicals. Items in this collection are those that are less than 7 pages long; lengthier materials from the Sinclair library have been individually cataloged.
Related Material
See Sinclair mss., Sinclair mss. II, Sinclair mss. III, Sinclair mss. IV, Sinclair mss. V, Sinclair mss. VI, Sinclair mss. VII, also located at the Lilly Library, Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana.
Acquisition Information
Purchase: 1957
Sinclair, Upton, 1878-1968
- [Miscellaneous Clippings on Upton Sinclair's The Jungle] (Box No Box)
  - 1. Dwyer, William M. Book penned around 1900 made your dinner good today. (From Trenton Sunday times. Nov. 15, 1964.) (Box No Box)
  - 2. Unger, Michael D. N.J. storm centered on Upton Sinclair; author tried for seclusion in Englewood cooperative dwelling." (From Trenton Sunday news. July 5, 1964.), PS3537.I85 J92 (Box No Box)
- Churchill, Winston, 1874–1965. The Chicago scandals: the novel which is making history / by Winston Spencer Churchill. (In P.T.O., edited by T.P. O'Connor. London. v. 1, no. 1–2, June 16 & 23, 1906. p. 25–26, 65–66), PS3537.I85 Z41377 (Box No Box)
- First British Reviews of The Flivver King, by Upton Sinclair. New York: U. Sinclair, [1937] 1 leaf; 14 x 22 cm., PS3537.I85 Z413772 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Glaspell, Susan, 1876–1948. George Cram Cook: a correction of Upton Sinclair's statement / by Susan Glaspell. (In Haldeman–Julius quarterly. v. 2, no. 3, Apr.–June 1928. p. 46), PS3537.I85 Z413774 (Box No Box)
- W., K. Marie Antoinette, by Upton Sinclair. New York: U. Sinclair, [1939] 1 leaf; 14 X 22 cm. Offprint from New York Times book review, July 30, 1939., PS3537.I85 Z49 2 copies (Box No Box)
- [Reviews of Upton Sinclair's Autobiography. New York: Harcourt, Brace & World, 1962] Fourteen clippings from various newspapers and magazines, many with penciled comments by Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z551 (Box No Box)
- [End Poverty in California (EPIC) campaign literature] 1934. 1 leaf; 78 mm. Anti–Sinclair campaign literature in the form of paper currency., PS3537.I85 Z5561 (Box No Box)
- Abbas, Khwaja Ahmad. Authors I have met ... / by Khwaja Ahmad Abbas. (In New book digest. Bombay, India. v. 4, no. 2, Aug. 1939. p. 13–17: ports.) Account of Sinclair, p. 15–16., PS3537.I85 Z578 (Box No Box)
- Abram, Sydney S. Upton Sinclair. (In The Fort George lantern: the literary arts magazine of George Washington High School, Fort George Hill, New York City. Oct. 1928. p. 33–38) Signed at end: Sydney S. Abram, '29. Author's inscribed copy to Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z58 (Box No Box)
- Adamic, Louis, 1899–1951. Upton Sinclair: a prophet of red dawn / by Louis Adamic. (In The open forum. Los Angeles. v. 4, no. 48, Nov. 26, 1927. p. 1–2), PS3537.I85 Z582 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Adimari, Ralph. Upton Sinclair, last of the dime novelists / by Ralph Adimari. (In Dime novel roundup. v. 24, no. 6–7, June 15, July 15, 1956. p. 42–44, 51–52: ill.), PS3537.I85 Z58202 (Box No Box)
- Aikman, Duncan, 1889– Thinking it over / by Duncan Aikman. (In Daily news. Los Angeles. v. 10, no. 143, Feb. 16, 1933. p. [16], 19) A discussion of "Upton Sinclair presents William Fox." Page 19 wanting., PS3537.I85 Z58203 (Box No Box)
- American colony in Bermuda is growing. (From New York World. Jan. 11, 1914) Included in the list of recent arrivals are the names of Mr. and Mrs. Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z58204 (Box No Box)
- Americkanische Dichter der Gegenwart. (From Sonderbeilage, Nr. 33 der "Deutsche Kurz–Post." Charlottenburg, 1929. [2] p.: ports.) Portraits and brief biographies of Upton Sinclair, Sinclair Lewis and Theodore Dreiser., PS3537.I85 Z58206 (Box No Box)
- Arden has a circus: clown rushes from ring and puts Sinclair under arrest. (From New York Times. Aug. 6, 1911) Aftermath of Sinclair's arrest for playing games on Sunday., PS3537.I85 Z5821 (Box No Box)
- Armour, Richard, 1906–1989. Upton Sinclair rips into John Barleycorn ... / by Richard Armour. (In an unidentified Pasadena, Calif. newspaper. Apr. 22, 1956. port.) A review of Sinclair's "The cup of fury.", PS3537.I85 Z58212 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Art's bar sinister. (From Rob Wagner's script. Beverly Hills, Calif. v. 4, no. 101, Jan. 17, 1931. p. 2), PS3537.I85 Z58213 (Box No Box)
- As Sinclair returns with injured wife "Tramp poet" Kemp sails as stowaway. (In New York evening journal. Sept. 30, 1913) Included are portraits of the first and second Mrs. Sinclair, Upton Sinclair and Harry Kemp [etc]. Harry Kemp was named by Sinclair as correspondent in his divorce proceedings against the first Mrs. Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z58216 (Box No Box)
- Astor, Vincent, 1891–1959. Astor writes to Sinclair. (From Appeal to reason. Girard, Kan. Jan. 24, 1914) An answer to Sinclair's letter which had appeared in an earlier issue of The appeal to reason., PS3537.I85 Z58218 (Box No Box)
- Axson, Stockton, 1867–1935. Floyd Dell's picture of Upton Sinclair is more than "A social protest" says Dr. Stockton Axson / by Dr. Stockton Axson. (From The chronicle. Houston, Texas. Aug. 21, 1927), PS3537.I85 Z5822 (Box No Box)
- B., A.S. Our doctored daily news. (From The Christian register. Aug. 5, 1920. p. 770) Review of The brass check, by Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z58222 (Box No Box)
- Bar Sinclair's plays. (From New York Sun. Jan. 27, 1909) Concerning Stanford University banning Upton Sinclair's Socialist plays., PS3537.I85 Z58225 (Box No Box)
- Barr, Margaret. A personal Jesus, by Upton Sinclair. (In The Aryan path. Bangalore, India. July 1955. p. 323) A review., PS3537.I85 Z58226 (Box No Box)
- Barrows, Edward Morley, 1887–1940. Upton Sinclair, whom you might call an "home incompris," as Floyd Dell interprets him ... / reviewed by Edward M. Barrows. (From The New York Post. Aug. 27, 1927) Review of Dell's "Upton Sinclair.", PS3537.I85 Z58227 (Box No Box)
- Barry, John D. (John Daniel), 1866–1942. Ways of the world: fine harvest / by John D. Barry. (In The San Francisco news. Oct. 19, 1940. p. 14) A review of Sinclair's "World's end.", PS3537.I85 Z58229 (Box No Box)
- Baskin, Alice Haines. Bust of Pasadena author is new work of noted Swedish sculptor ... / by Alice Haines Baskin. (From Pasadena Star–News. July 23, 1926. ill.), PS3537.I85 Z5823 (Box No Box)
- Bates, H. E. (Herbert Ernest), 1905–1974. Two giants and a giant killer / by H. E. Bates. (In The new clarion. June 25, 1932. p. 62) Reviews of Candid reminiscences, by Upton Sinclair; Lenin, by J. Maxton; Frank Harris, by Hugh Kingsmill; Ten contemporaries, by John Gawsworth., PS3537.I85 Z58233 (Box No Box)
- Beatty, Bessie, 1886–1947. Offered self for sale, now Sinclair's star: Miss Elizabeth Magie, who will be leading woman. (In San Francisco Bulletin. Jan. 26, 1909. p. [2]: port.), PS3537.I85 Z58235 (Box No Box)
- Beaufort, John. Off Broadway's venturesome enterprise / by John Beaufort. (In The Christian Science monitor. Feb. 11, 1961) Proof copies. A favorable review of Sinclair's play "Cicero.", PS3537.I85 Z58237 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Bell, Thomas H. [Letter to the editor] (In The open forum. v. 2, no. 32. p. 3) Castigating Sinclair for his defense of the treatment of political prisoners in Russia., PS3537.I85 Z5824 (Box No Box)
- Benchley, Robert, 1889–1945. Books and other things / by Robert C. Benchley. (From The New York World. Sept. 8, 1920) Benchley's criticism of Sinclair's "The brass check.", PS3537.I85 Z58244 (Box No Box)
- Bennett, Jesse Lee, 1885–1931. Civil liberty in Los Angeles. [Los Angeles: Southern California Branch of the American Civil Liberties Union, 1923] [4]p.; 12mo. Caption title. Offprint "from ... the Baltimore Sun, May 24, 1923.", PS3537.I85 Z5825 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Benton, W. C. The progress of labor / by W. C. Benton. Cincinnati, 1992. 1 leaf: ill.; 36 cm. At bottom of page: "Free advertisement" [for U. Sinclair's "The brass check."], PS3537.I85 Z58254 (Box No Box)
- Bergendahl, Erling. Upton Sinclair — Sacco og Vanzetti / av Erling Bergendahl. (In Arbeiderbladet. Apr. 6, 1929. p. 4: ports.), PS3537.I85 Z582546 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Berry, Graham. Upton Sinclair near 78 and he's still crusading ... / by Graham Berry. (In Los Angeles Times. Aug. 26, 1956. p. 1, 6: ill., port.), PS3537.I85 Z5825462 (Box No Box)
- Bohn, Wm. E. (William Edward), b. 1877. Sinclair: the writer as a good man. (In The new leader. v. 41, no. 34, Sept. 22, 1958. p. 23: port.), PS3537.I85 Z5825464 (Box No Box)
- [Book reviews] (In The English literary and educational review for continental readers. Leipzig. no. 3, Autumn 1932. p. 10, 16–18, 24) Reviews of Sinclair's The goose–step, American outpost, The wet parade., PS3537.I85 Z58256 (Box No Box)
- Breit, Harvey, 1913– In and out of books / by Harvey Breit. (In The New York Times book review. Feb. 3, 1957. p. 8: ill.) Preview of Sinclair's "My life in letters.", PS3537.I85 Z5827 (Box No Box)
- Broun, Heywood, 1888–1939. Books / by Heywood Broun. (From The New York Tribune. May 3, 1920) Takes issue with Sinclair in his attack on the newspaper treatment of his novel "The brass check.", PS3537.I85 Z5828 (Box No Box)
- Broun, Heywood, 1888–1939. Books / by Heywood Broun. (From The New York Tribune. Aug. 27, 1920) A discussion of his attitude toward Sinclair's "The brass check.", PS3537.I85 Z582801 (Box No Box)
- Brown, William Garrott, 1868–1913. Prophetic voices about America / by William Garrott Brown. (From an unidentified periodical [ca. 1907]. p. 372–383) Among the authors and works discussed is The industrial republic, by Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z58281 (Box No Box)
- Bruccoli, Matthew J. (Matthew Joseph), 1931–2008. A grievance against the demon rum ... / by M.J. Bruccoli. (In The Richmond news leader. May 5, 1956. p. 8: port.) A review of Sinclair's "The cup of fury.", PS3537.I85 Z582812 (Box No Box)
- Burgum, Edwin Berry, b. 1894. Lanny Budd marches on ... / by Edwin Berry Burgum. (In The New York Times book review. June 10, 1945. p. 5, 8: port.) A review of "Dragon Harvest.", PS3537.I85 Z582813 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Burton, Jean, 1910– The EPIC beehive of Mr. Upton Sinclair / by Jean Burton. (In New democracy. Sept. 15, 1934. p. 26–28), PS3537.I85 Z582814 (Box No Box)
- C., G.R. Upton Sinclair, man of the month. (In The peninsulan. v. 2, no. 11, Sept. 1934. p. 7–8, 24) Article signed at end: G.R.C., PS3537.I85 Z582818 (Box No Box)
- C., S.T. "The wet parade" (In Saturday night. Nov. 14, 1931. p. 14–15) Book review., PS3537.I85 Z58282 (Box No Box)
- The whirlwind of Sinclairism: a challenge to action, a call to arms in defense of California. San Francisco: California League Against Sinclairism, 1934. 1 p. A political advertisement taken from The Argonaut, October 19, 1934., PS3537.I85 Z58284 (Box No Box)
- Calverton, V. F. (Victor Francis), 1900–1940. Social forces in late American literature / by V. F. Calverton. (From The workers monthly. Chicago. Sept. 1925. p. 509–512) Discusses Sinclair as the pessimist with faith in the reconstruction of value through the rise of his class., PS3537.I85 Z5829 (Box No Box)
- Camphorated oil. (In Cambridge magazine. Cambridge, [Eng.] v. 8, no. 40, July 12, 1919. p. [1]) Comment on Sinclair's "The profits of religion.", PS3537.I85 Z58294 (Box No Box)
- Carew, Harold D. (Harold David), b. 1890. 'Between two worlds': Upton Sinclair, at zenith of power, pens smashing novel of mad twenties / by Harold D. Carew. (In Pasadena Star–News. Mar. 29, 1941. p. 11: ill., port.) A review of Sinclair's "Between two worlds.", PS3537.I85 Z58298 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Carew, Harold D. (Harold David), b. 1890. Upton Sinclair as a prohibitionist: the forces that have misrepresented and abused this noted author and reformer are now training their guns on prohibition leaders / Harold D. Carew. (In Zion's herald. Oct. 29, 1930. p. 1386–1387: port.), PS3537.I85 Z583 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Carew, Harold D. (Harold David), b. 1890. Upton Sinclair, the prophet: a study in social protest / by Harold D. Carew. (From Pasadena Star–News. Sept. 17, 1927. p. [16]) Review of F. Dell's Upton Sinclair, a study in social protest., PS3537.I85 Z584 (Box No Box)
- Carnegie, Dale, 1888–1955. Upton Sinclair, the most widely read living author went hungry for years. (In Newcomerstown news and Index. Newcomerstown, Ohio. v. 41, no. 18, Jan. 5, 1939. p. [1], 8) At head of title: Dale Carnegie: five minute biographies., PS3537.I85 Z5837 (Box No Box)
- [Cartoon on "The profits of religion"] (From the Kansas City Star. June 24, 1920. 1 p.), PS3537.I85 Z585 (Box No Box)
- The case of Sinclair. (In The capital times. Madison, Wisc. May 2, 1922. p. 12), PS3537.I85 Z5854 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Chapman, Rose Woodallen, 1875–1923. Upton Sinclair's experiment: a unique housekeeping venture originated by the author of "The jungle" and the way it is working out / by Rose Woodallen Chapman. (From Good health. 1907. p. 169–174: ill., port.) Just as this article went to press there came the news of the destruction by the fire of Helicon Hall., PS3537.I85 Z587 (Box No Box)
- Cherrington, Ernest Hurst, 1877–1950. Review of The wet parade, by Upton Sinclair, published by Farra & Rinehart ... / by Ernest H. Cherrington. [1931] 2 p. Typed copy., PS3537.I85 Z588 (Box No Box)
- Churchill, Douglas W. Upton Sinclair, 60, looks back on his crusades. In The New York Times magazine. Sept. 18, 1938. p. 7, 22: port.), PS3537.I85 Z5881 (Box No Box)
- [Clipping announcing the forthcoming marriage of Upton Sinclair's first wife] (From Court journal. Paris. June 26, 1913), PS3537.I85 Z5882 (Box No Box)
- Cohen, Sid Q. Sinclair presents a wailing Fox. (In Call of youth. v. 1, no. 5, May 1933. p. 7: port.) A review of "Upton Sinclair presents William Fox.", PS3537.I85 Z5883 (Box No Box)
- Awards of Pulitzer prizes and traveling scholarships made by the Trustees of Columbia University on the recommendations of the Advisory Board of the Graduate School of Journalism, May 3, 1943. New York, 1943. 3 p.; 4to. Among the prizes listed is that of $500 to Upton Sinclair "for a distinguished novel published during the year by an American author" for his novel "Dragon's teeth.", PS3537.I85 Z5884 (Box No Box)
- Come on over, Upton. (In Pacific weekly. Carmel, Calif. v. 4, no. 19. p. 258) An editorial., PS3537.I85 Z5885 (Box No Box)
- [Comment on Sinclair's article on Edward McDowell in the January number of The American Mercury] (From the New York Times. Jan. 17, 1925. 1 p.), PS3537.I85 Z5886 (Box No Box)
- Communications. (In the Daily Princetonian. Nov. 19, 1935) A series of four anonymous letters concerning a speech made by Sinclair at the University., PS3537.I85 Z5887 (Box No Box)
- Communists' report on S.L. all wrong, novelist informed. (From the Deseret News. Salt Lake City, Utah. Dec. 3, 1931), PS3537.I85 Z5888 (Box No Box)
- Co–op. (In Thutgauer Arbeiterzeitung. v. 26, no. 201, Aug. 1937) An unsigned criticism of the book., PS3537.I85 Z58884 (Box No Box)
- Craig, William Warren, 1883– Upton Sinclair, nonconformer: an admirable biography / by Will Craig. (From The Union voice for the trade union room and home. Melbourne. v. 7, no. 68, Sept. 14, 1929. p. 1: port.) In part, a review of Floyd Dell's biography of Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z59 (Box No Box)
- Cramer, Madelyn A. Defends Sinclair. (In The Pacific weekly. v.4, no.17, Apr. 27, 1936. p. 238) A letter to the editor., PS3537.I85 Z591 (Box No Box)
- Creel, George, 1876–1953. Utopia unlimited / by George Creel. (From The Saturday evening post. v. 207, no. 21, Nov. 24, 1954. p. 5–7, 78–80.: ill., ports.), PS3537.I85 Z592 (Box No Box)
- Cubeiro, D. Petroleo, la última novela de Upton Sinclair. (From Claridad. Oct. 12, 1927) Book review., PS3537.I85 Z593 (Box No Box)
- "The Cup of Fury" (In National voice. Los Angeles. v. 86, no. 16, Aug. 2, 1956. p. 1, 5: ill., port.) A review of the book; includes opinions of the book by various readers., PS3537.I85 Z594 (Box No Box)
- De Casseres, Benjamin, 1873–1945. Letter to the Editor. (From Contempo. Chapel Hill, N.C. v. 1, Nov. 15, 1931), PS3537.I85 Z596 (Box No Box)
- Dell, Floyd, 1887–1969. Upton Sinclair. (In Bokstugan: studiecirklarnas tidskrift. arg. 13, nr. 3, Mar. 1929. p. 79–83) A review of Dell's biography of Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z6781 (Box No Box)
- Deutsch, Babette, 1895–1982. A moot point. (In New York Herald–Tribune. Aug. 28, 1927) A review of Floyd Dell's "Upton Sinclair.", PS3537.I85 Z6786 (Box No Box)
- Do Socialists want Socialism? (In The Christian century. Sept. 19, 1934. p. 1167–1169) A discussion of Sinclair's campaign for governor of California., PS3537.I85 Z6801 (Box No Box)
- Dorsey, John. Upton Sinclair relives his Baltimore childhood / story by John Dorsey; photos by William L. Klender. (In The Sun magazine section. Baltimore. Oct. 10, 1965. p. 16–18: ill., ports.) Autographed presentation copy signed: Upton., PS3537.I85 Z68015 (Box No Box)
- "Dragon's teeth" in England. (From The Manchester guardian. July 24, 1942. 1 leaf; 8 x 20 cm.), PS3537.I85 Z68024 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Drei, die an einem Strang ziehen! (In Die Arbeiter–illustrierte Zeitung aller Länder. Reichenberg. Jahrg. 8, Nr. 21, Juni 1, 1929. p. 1) Full page portraits of Upton Sinclair, Charlie Chaplin and Egon Erwin Kisch., PS3537.I85 Z6803 (Box No Box)
- Dreiser, Theodore, 1871–1945. Upton Sinclair / by Theodore Dreiser. (In The clipper. v.1, no.2, Sept. 1940. p. 3–4), PS3537.I85 Z6804 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Drury, John, 1898– The book that blew up the stockyards: social and industrial reforms were the aftermath of the books' fictionalized revelations / by John Drury. (In The butcher workman. May–June 1961. p. 11–13, 32: ill., ports.), PS3537.I85 Z6806 (Box No Box)
- Duffus, R. L. (Robert Luther), 1888–1972. A model's commission ... / by R.L. Duffus. (From The reporter. 1961) A review of Sinclair's "Affectionately Eve.", PS3537.I85 Z68066 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Duffus, R. L. (Robert Luther), 1888–1972. A new novel by Upton Sinclair: in "World's end" the artist triumphs over the pamphleteer ... / by R.L. Duffus. (In The New York Times book review. June 16, 1940. p. 1, 19: ports.), PS3537.I85 Z6807 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Duffus, R. L. (Robert Luther), 1888–1972. The progress of a pamphleteer: Upton Sinclair and his hero Lanny Budd move on to the twilight sleep of Munich ... / by R.L. Duffus. (In The New York Times book review. June 4, 1944. p. 1, 29: ports.) Review of Sinclair's "Presidential agent." Included in this issue is a full page advertisement for the book [p. 17]., PS3537.I85 Z6808 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Dunne, Finley Peter, 1867–1936. Mr. Dooley on the food we eat / by F.P. Dunne. (From Collier's. June 23, 1906. p. 15–16) Concerning The jungle., PS3537.I85 Z681 (Box No Box)
- Dyer, George F. With kind regards to Mr. Upton Sinclair. (In The conserver. Los Angeles. v. 1, no. 42, Apr. 23, 1931. p. [1]–2) Article signed at end: George F. Dyer., PS3537.I85 Z6814 (Box No Box)
- Eastman, Max, 1883–1969. Is this the truth about Sacco and Vanzetti? / Max Eastman. (In National review. v. 11, no. 16, Oct. 21, 1961. p. 261–264) Quotes extensively from Sinclair's opinions and evaluates these opinions., PS3537.I85 Z6815 (Box No Box)
- Echoes from bow bells. (From Bellman. Minneapolis. Apr. 20, 1910) Among other topics discussed, is a comment on Sinclair's article on "Perfect health" in the April number of the Contemporary review., PS3537.I85 Z6816 (Box No Box)
- The editor's viewpoint. (From Physical culture. New York. July 1910. p. 1–2) Comment on Sinclair's "Fasting for health" in the Cosmopolitan magazine., PS3537.I85 Z68163 (Box No Box)
- Einstein, Albert, 1879–1955. [Introductory statement from Sinclair's Mental radio] [1930] 1 leaf; 8 x 14 cm., PS3537.I85 Z6817 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Register Democratic now!: so you can vote for Upton Sinclair in the primaries! [Los Angeles: End Poverty League, inc., 1934] [4] p.: port.; 12mo., PS3537.I85 Z6818 (Box No Box)
- Epic heads split wide open: Sinclair breaks with Sen. Olson, Packard, Stitt Wilson and other liberal leaders. (In Independent review. Los Angeles. Feb. 25, 1936. p. [1], 3), PS3537.I85 Z6819 (Box No Box)
- EPIC in California. 5 v. Scrapbooks compiled by Frederick W. Nelson and Lucile C. Nelson. Contents: v. 1–2, The great gubernatorial campaign, 1934. –– v. 3, The Epic movement, Jan.–June 1935. –– v. 4, The Epic movement, June–Dec. 1935. –– v. 5, The Presidential election, 1936., PS3537.I85 Z68194 (Box No Box)
- Evans, I. O. (Idrisyn Oliver), 1894–1977. The art of Upton Sinclair / by I.O. Evans. (From Civil service arts magazine. Winter 1932. p. [114]–115), PS3537.I85 Z682 (Box No Box)
- Event extraordinary! Sinclair to play violin. (In The open forum. Los Angeles. v. 6, no. 39, Sept. 28, 1929. p. [1]) A news item, in a box on front page., PS3537.I85 Z683 (Box No Box)
- Fairchild, Henry Pratt, 1880–1956. Reynard foxed. (In The new republic. Apr. 19, 1933. p. 287–288.) A review of "Upton Sinclair presents William Fox.", PS3537.I85 Z68305 (Box No Box)
- The fasting cure, by Upton Sinclair. London, W. Heinemann, 1911. (From Nature magazine. July 25, 1912) Book review., PS3537.I85 Z683102 (Box No Box)
- Favorite novelists of Autralia. [S.l.: s.n., s.d.] 1 leaf; 9 x 15 cm. Upton Sinclair ranks third among living novelists., PS3537.I85 Z6832 2 copies (Box No Box)
- Feder, Ernst, 1881–1964. Besuch bei Upton Sinclair. " Wenn ic Gouverneur ware ..." / von Dr. Ernst Feder. (From Berliner Tageblatt. Nr. 324, Juli 12, 1930), PS3537.I85 Z68325 (Box No Box)
- Few 'Brass checks' in the press today. (In The guild reporter. v. 28, no. 7, Mar. 24, 1961. p. 7), PS3537.I85 Z68326 (Box No Box)
- First truckload of 'Flivver kings' arrives at auto union headquarters. (In The progressive. Detroit. 1937) Picture of books arriving, with caption., PS3537.I85 Z68327 (Box No Box)
- 525 titles in 34 countries. (From The world tomorrow. Nov. 1930. p. 439) A new item commenting upon the great influence of Upton Sinclair., PS3537.I85 Z6833 (Box No Box)
- 'Flivver king' out October 15. (In United Automobile Worker. Detroit. Sept. 25, 1937. p. 9: port.), PS3537.I85 Z6835 (Box No Box)
- Fox–filmed, by Upton Sinclair who scores high finance. (In News–week. Feb. 25, 1933. p. 27: port.), PS3537.I85 Z68354 (Box No Box)
- Garrett, Eileen J. (Eileen Jeanette), 1893–1970. Presidential agent, by Upton Sinclair / reviewed by Eileen J. Garrett. (In Tomorrow. v. 4, no. 1, Sept. 1944. p. 83), PS3537.I85 Z6836 (Box No Box)
- Glass, Montague, 1877–1934. Abe and Mawruss dig into this Nobel prize problem / by Montague Glass. (From The Los Angeles Examiner. Los Angeles, 1931. 1 p.), PS3537.I85 Z6837 (Box No Box)
- Goldberg, Isaac, 1887–1938. In the world of books / by Isaac Goldberg. (From The Haldeman–Julius weekly. Girard, Kan. Aug. 20, 1927. 1 p.) Book review of Floyd Dell's "Upton Sinclair.", PS3537.I85 Z6838 (Box No Box)
- Gottesman, Ronald. Segei Eisenstein & Upton Sinclair / Ronald Gottesman. [London: British Film Institute, 1965] 2 leaves; 4to. 2 leaves Xeroxed from Sight and sound, summer issue, 1965., PS3537.I85 Z6839 (Box No Box)